Okay, so I'm gonna show you guys some surge gameplay.
If you watch pro matches, they pick surge to counter someone like Poco, Tank, or just
Daniel Grassy Brawler.
But obviously there's some counters to surge, so I don't think it's like one of the best
Brawlers, but still he's really good.
So yeah, let's play some matches.
I mean, surge is pretty good in this spinning mode, so yeah, this clown needs a spinning
bro.
I'm pretty sure he's gonna like sneaking.
Yeah, he can't even stay in the bushes, he's pretty good.
Okay, there are more timers, but we can definitely get the kill on this guy, because
it's my super and yeah, thank you for the power cube.
I mean, so far so good, like we're doing well.
But there are another timers on the right, like please play the game.
This guy is even using the thumbs down bro, and yeah, I mean, there are just so many timers.
Okay, so there's a Janet with the gadget.
We need to watch out.
Okay, there was a nice kill.
Got to watch out this bike though.
Gonna use my gadget just in case.
Okay, that was pretty good.
I don't wanna give him any power cubes, so I'm gonna go aggressive.
Maybe he can get the kill?
No.
Okay, he's pretty smart, I guess.
So I'm just gonna regen.
I mean, it's just sort of to get the kill on Nive, especially when he has a gadget, so
some clowns in the mid, they're just spinning, not playing the game.
Let's just get the kill on Nive, like this guy is the reason why I can't go mid.
Yeah, he can't even use the gadget, so now it's just me versus tank.
So it's pretty much over.
They can't really kill me unless I don't have a super.
So we're just gonna stay in the mid and get the kill on there.
We'll give me some ammo.
Okay, and we're gonna get the kill on this dumb, dumb, pretty much well.
I mean, this is definitely the best matchup for surge.
I feel like Brobel is probably his best mode because you're gonna face a lot of tanks,
you know?
And yeah, I gotta watch out this dynamite.
I'm gonna get stunned, that was definitely my bad.
As long as I get my super, I can make a play.
Okay, goodnight, the super and get the kill.
And once you get the speed, there is almost no counter, so you can definitely go more aggressive.
We can get the kill on dynamite.
We're gonna use my gadget to stay alive and just wait for the surge to use the super and get the kill.
Kind of popping off right now.
Get the kill again, use the super and the gadget to stay alive.
I think we can definitely score this, please.
Okay, Leon is using the super, so please watch out, BB, please.
No, he's gonna go down.
But it doesn't really matter, I can get the kill.
Gonna watch out this super, pass it to Nida and he's gonna score.
We are gonna face some sweaty comp.
Like Poco, Lu and Ash are really good, so.
Okay, got my super, so I can go aggressive with the super here and, okay.
I actually got a double kill, so that's really good.
I mean, we got the mid control, so we just gotta hold it.
I'm gonna save my super so they can't go aggressive, you know?
Yeah, let's do what I can do here.
I'm gonna use my super and maybe make a play with the gadget, please.
Okay, got the kill on Ash.
I'm kinda popping off right now.
And get a kill on Poco as well.
Yeah, we're winning by 70%, so I think we should be fine.
This Frank needs to stop feeding the loose super.
Like, they're just so many loose super on the map right now.
I think we should be fine still, we're winning by 60%.
Just get into the zone and, yeah, stay there.
I don't have a gadget, so I can't really carry, but.
Like, now we just stay like, like, just stop dying, please.
Frank, our bow went down again.
Like, we just need four more percent.
Please stop dying.
Like Frank, this bow is gonna go down as well.
This is gonna be actually the close match.
There's no way.
Just get into the zone, please, okay?
That's how you do it.
Okay, we're facing another sweaty comp, so just give me the Ash lane,
then we should be fine.
Okay, we're facing Ash, so like, once you get a super,
you can just go aggressive and use the gadget.
Okay, got my super, and now I can use the super in the gadget
and get a kill.
Okay, our crow is gonna go down, but it doesn't really matter.
I can definitely hold my lane, so just keep the distance
until you get a super, and once you get a super,
you can go aggressive.
This crow is gonna use the super.
I'm gonna go aggressive as well, since they wasted all the ammo.
Okay, let's see what we can do here.
They're all on the right.
I'm gonna use the super and use the gadget
and get a double kill, okay?
Kinda popping off right now, and we can get a kill on Pany as well
with the super, okay?
Got another kill on Ash.
Honestly, I kinda carried the match, and yeah,
there was a pretty clean match.
We were facing some sweaty team, but we were gonna place
some basketball, and we got the underdog, okay?
So, that means we're facing some decent players, I think.
I don't have a good matchup, so I need to get my super
as soon as possible, so I can get the speed.
Our teammates are gonna go down,
at least I got my super, so let's see what I can do here.
I'm gonna go down to Colette, but really good gadget by Fang.
I mean, they do have a really hard counter comp, so yeah.
Nevermind, this Fang is just different.
Okay, they're using the dumpstown, I think we're good.
I'm gonna use the super, I almost went down to B, but we're still alive, you know?
And I'm gonna use the gadget to stay alive.
Just tank the B shot, yep.
And yeah, looking so far, our Fang is popping off.
We can definitely score here, gonna pass it to both.
And he's not gonna score, but I'm gonna use my super here
to get a kill, and this Fang is just a goat.
You can just tank some shots, so you can score.
Let's go.
Yeah, we're facing some sweaty team again, yeah, GG.
Okay, so this is probably the only mode
that you need to avoid, because I feel like all the maps right now in Naka,
they're all kinda open maps, so you can get easily outraged by so many brawlers.
So you need to bring this gadget and get a speed, so you can get a super.
But like once you get this super, like I said,
there are almost no counters, so you can definitely do some work.
Okay, we kinda push them back, they're using the thumbs down.
I'm kinda dodging so many shots.
And we can definitely get a kill here, okay?
Got a kill and a block, gonna use the super to stay alive.
Now we can pinch, grumb here.
Okay, nice kill.
And this is 2B1 situation, so...
I don't think we're gonna lose this one.
Okay, that was pretty close.
This ghost got a super, so...
He's gonna use the super actually, and actually he's kinda popping off.
We need to watch out for sure.
Okay, actually I'm gonna go down to ghost.
That was really close.
Yeah, I mean, now I got my super, so I can just use the gadget
to get the next range and just dodging so many shots right now.
Brom, different with the surge.
Yeah, got a kill.
They're gonna use the thumbs down, we're good.
Gonna get another kill and...
Honestly, I kinda carry the match again.
Yeah.
We were facing another good team, so GG.
And yeah, thank you guys for watching,
and I'll see you guys on the next one.